Priyesh Rajasekaran

priyesh2103@gmail.com | 979-985-9266

Summary

5+ years of experience in designing and leading enterprise wide implementation of technology products focused on tech strategy, financial planning and workforce management. Experienced with product release cycles and have proven global track record of delivering technology driven business growth.

Education

Mays Business School, Texas A&M University

College Station, USA

Master of Science in Management Information Systems, GPA 3.9

May 2017

GMAT: 740 /800 (97th Percentile)

SSN College of Engineering, Anna University

Chennai, India

Bachelor of Engineering in Electrical and Electronics, GPA 3.6

May 2012

Skills & Expertise

Technical Skills: SQL-PL SQL, Database Design, Data Analysis & Visualization

Industry Verticals: Retail, Franchise Operations, Technology, Fintech

Functional Skills: Business Process Design, Workforce Management, Tech Investment Planning, Project Planning,

Product Implementation

Professional Experience

⇒ Intuit Mountain View, CA

Senior Business Systems Analyst | Technology Business Management

May 2017 – Present

- Conceptualized, designed and successfully rolled out the Tech Investment Planning Process, bringing together
 multiple groups on to a common platform for a unified and efficient planning process, delivering 2%
 technology cost savings.
- Developed and rolled out a contingent workforce tracking mechanism and dashboard to gather data, understand and track the CW landscape across Intuit.
- Assisted in setting up success metrics and improving user experience for Better works t4i roll-out; achieved a 4% increase in employee engagement over the quarter.
- **t4i Org Evolution Roles Marketplace Experiment Lead:** Part of the three-member team leading the effort on experimenting, prototyping and implementing a "Roles Marketplace" platform for Intuit
- Leading the Technology Business Management Group and played a central role in hiring and mentoring of business analysts in Business Ops Group

Intuit Innovation Catalyst: Part of the Intuit Innovation Catalyst Community, responsible designing and developing product design techniques using customer driven innovation (2018-Present)

⇒ M.H. Alshaya Co. W.L.L.,

Safat, Kuwait

Application Solutions Engineer | Application Ops

October 2012 - May 2015

- Designed and implemented an enterprise system to perform real time sales and inventory data management, revenue tracking and financial reporting for outlets of multiple retail brands across MENA, Europe and UK, facilitating a 7% cost reduction over 3 years
- Lead engineer for **Food Services Labor Planning Application** design and roll out, across 12 markets in the MENA region, leading to increased operational efficiency
- Appointed lead trainer to hire and mentor a team of 7 new employees (~20 months in) Conducted a 90-day training program focusing on Application Development, implementation of internal controls and adherence to SLAs